sqwosh.com 2016-09-04

# Privacy Policy : SEO Friendly Directory, Local Business Directory, Online Business Directory, Local Business Listings

Featured 

Top categories 

New listings 

[Thailand's Leading Family Lawyer - Prenuptial Agreement in Thailand](http://www.sqwosh.com/business/business-law/thailand-s-leading-family-lawyer-prenuptial-agreement-in-thailand-l7858.html)

New Articles 

Search by articles 

|  **Search by articles**  
---  
  
PageRanks 

[

7/10

](http://www.sqwosh.com/pagerank7-listings.html) | **2**  
---|---  
[

6/10

](http://www.sqwosh.com/pagerank6-listings.html) | **9**  
[

5/10

](http://www.sqwosh.com/pagerank5-listings.html) | **19**  
[

4/10

](http://www.sqwosh.com/pagerank4-listings.html) | **104**  
[

3/10

](http://www.sqwosh.com/pagerank3-listings.html) | **288**  
[

2/10

](http://www.sqwosh.com/pagerank2-listings.html) | **396**  
[

1/10

](http://www.sqwosh.com/pagerank1-listings.html) | **392**  
  
New Admin Articles 

[A Great Way To Give Your Business A Boost: Internet Marketing](http://www.sqwosh.com/blog/A-Great-Way-To-Give-Your-Business-A-Boost-Internet-Marketing-a3.html)

Newsletter 

**Real name:**  

**Email:**  

[SQWOSH ](http://www.sqwosh.com/) /  **Privacy Policy**

Search By Locations 

| Search: | Location:  
---|---  
|   
  
This policy explains the what, how, and why of the information we collect when you use our Website.  
Your Privacy is extremely seriously for us, and we never sell any information.

###  Definitions

We’ll start by getting a few definitions out of the way that should help you understand this policy. When we say “we,” and “us,” we refer to SQWOSH.Com.  
When we say our Website, we refer to SQWOSH.Com. 

###  Scope

This Privacy Policy is effective with respect to any data that we’ve collected, or collect, about and/or from you, according to our [Terms of Use](http://www.link-your-site.com/terms.html).

###  Questions & Concerns

If you have any questions or comments, or if you want to update, delete, or change any Personal Information we hold, or you have a concern about the way in which we have handled any privacy matter please use our [contact form](http://www.sqwosh.com/mod/contacts/?contact=us) to get in touch. You may also contact us by postal mail or email at:

###  MiaC Corp.   
23 Vasileos Pavlou   
Kaimakli  
Nicosia 1023  
Cyprus 

###  Email: contact@sqwosh.com  
Telephone: +357 99 262 115

###  Information We Collect

  1. **Information You Provide to Us:**  When you use the Services, consult with our customer service team, send us an email, post on our blog, or communicate with us in any way, you’re giving us information that we collect. Information may include your IP address, name, physical address, email address, phone number, as well as details like gender, occupation, location, birth date, purchase history, and other demographic information. By giving us this information. We NEVER collect Credit Card information. 

  2. **Information from your Use of the Service** : We may get information about how and when you use the Services, store it in log files associated with your account, and link it to other information we collect about you. This information may include, for example, your IP address, time, date, browser used, and actions you’ve taken within the application.

  3. **Cookies and Tracking** : When you use our Website, we may store “cookies,” “tags,” or “scripts,” which are strings of code, on your computer. We and our analytics Service Providers (like [Google](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)) use those cookies to collect information about your visit and your use of our Website or Services. You may turn off cookies that have been placed on your computer by following the instructions on your browser, but if you block cookies, it may be more difficult (and maybe even impossible) to use some aspects of the Services.

Thanks for taking the time to learn about our Privacy Policy. 

_Updated May 19, 2016_

|   
---|---  
  
Accounts area 

Username:

Password:

Popular categories 

[Business](http://www.sqwosh.com/business/) 6756

[Computers](http://www.sqwosh.com/computers/) 3142

[Shopping](http://www.sqwosh.com/shopping/) 2921

[Health](http://www.sqwosh.com/health/) 2012

[Recreation](http://www.sqwosh.com/recreation/) 1536

[Travel](http://www.sqwosh.com/recreation/travel/) 1290

[Business Services](http://www.sqwosh.com/business/business-services/) 923

[Internet](http://www.sqwosh.com/computers/internet/) 887

[Society](http://www.sqwosh.com/society/) 860

[Real Estate](http://www.sqwosh.com/business/real-estate/) 858

Top listings 

[Affordable Limo Cars Melbourne | Melbourne Best Wedding Cars | Airport limos Melbourne](http://www.sqwosh.com/business/business-services/affordable-limo-cars-melbourne-melbourne-best-wedding-cars-airport-limos-melbourne-l7835.html)

Tags
